{
  "code": "0000",
  "description": "oh yeah,通过了",
  "result": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": "1",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "What's your name?\n____ name is Civa.",
        "answers": "My,you,your",
        "right": "My"
      },
      {
        "id": "2",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "___ this?\nIt's an egg.",
        "answers": "What,How,What's",
        "right": "What's"
      },
      {
        "id": "3",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "That is __ orange.",
        "answers": "a,the,an",
        "right": "an"
      },
      {
        "id": "4",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "This is __ ruler.",
        "answers": "a,the,an",
        "right": "a"
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "___ sister is Mary.",
        "answers": "She,He,Her",
        "right": "Her"
      },
      {
        "id": "6",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "Is it ____ cup?",
        "answers": "My,you,your",
        "right": "your"
      },
      {
        "id": "7",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "翻译：他们是朋友。\nThey are _____.",
        "answers": "a friend,friends,friend",
        "right": "friends"
      },
      {
        "id": "8",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "Tony and Nick ___ classmates.",
        "answers": "are,is,am",
        "right": "are"
      },
      {
        "id": "9",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "Are these his book?\nYes, ___ are",
        "answers": "these,those,they",
        "right": "they"
      },
      {
        "id": "10",
        "grade": "primary_school",
        "question": "They ___ my books.Mine are at school.",
        "answers": "aren't,are,not",
        "right": "aren't"
      }
    ]
  },
  "success": "true"
}